<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bijay Gaudel</title>
    <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bijay Gaudel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:04:37 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gaudelbijay.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 21:06:00 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Image Quality Assessment I did this project under the supervision of Prof. Ukash Nakarmi from university of Arkansas. In this Project, we explore several convolutional neural network-based frameworks and different data augmentation technique for medical image quality assessment. We used nearest neighbor loss function as a regularizer which helps to find the best model in less epoch. We used Wavelet transform methods to decompose image into images of same classes and train the model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 21:05:44 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Gaudel B., Guan D., Yuan W., Shrestha D., Chen B., Tu Y. (2021) Graph Representation Learning Using Attention Network. In: Mei H. et al. (eds) Big Data. BigData 2020. Communications in Computer and Information Science, vol 1320. Springer, Singapore. https://doi.org/10.1007/978-981-16-0705-9_10
  Bijay Gaudel, Deepanjal Shrestha, Niosh Basnet, Donghai Guan. Link Prediction in Bipartite Network using Composite Similarities. IEEE Access . (Submitted)
  Bikash Nakarmi, Hao Chen, Ikechi Augustine Ukaegbu, Bijay Gaudel, Ukash Nakarmi, Saravanan Muthaiyan, Wang Xiang Chuan, Shilong Pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Action Values</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/estimating_action_values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 17:04:37 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/estimating_action_values/</guid>
      <description>By the end of this post you will learn to:
 Estimate action values using the sample average method. Describe greedy action selection. Introduce the exploration-exploitation dilemma. Describe how action values can be estimated incrementally using the sample-average method. Identify how the incremental update rule is an instance of a more general update rule. Describe how the general update rule can be used to solve a non-stationary bandit problem.  Value of Action The value of action is the expected reward when the action is taken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The K-armed Bandit Problem</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/bandit_problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 21:51:00 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/bandit_problem/</guid>
      <description>In this post we will formalize the problem of decision making under uncertanity using k-armed bandits. We will define fundamental concepts like : rewards, time steps and values.
In the k-armed bandit problem, we have an agent who chooses between k actions and recives a reward based on the action it chooses.
medication example of K-armed bandit For example a doctor is giving 3 different medication to 3 different patients with same problem and observed the effect of medication in patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 23:45:54 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/quotes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Normal people continue the world, genius are those who change it&amp;rdquo; ― Bijay Gaudel (Myself)
LIFE “The past is already gone, the future is not yet here. There’s only one moment for you to live.”- Gautama Buddha
&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t have to see the whole staircase. Just take the first step.&amp;rdquo; ― Martin Luther King
“Be realistic: Plan for a miracle” ― Osho
“Never let the fear of striking out keep you from playing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 21:20:54 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>gaudelbijay10@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 21:17:36 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Computer Science graduate from Nanjing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics, Nanjing, China, advised by Prof. Donghai Guan. For my graduate research, I worked on complex network analysis using graph representation learning. In my 4th semenster of masters degree, I worked on an Image Quality Assessment project under the supervision of Prof. Ukash Nakarmi. I found these problems particularly exciting because of the subjective nature of these tasks and, in some cases, the difficulty in capturing sufficient training data poses an interesting challenge in terms of training with limited/noisy data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famous Convolution Neural Network Architectures</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/cnn_architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:09:00 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/cnn_architecture/</guid>
      <description>LeNet-5 Architecture     VGG-16 Architecture     ResNet Architecture     AlexNet Architecture     Inception Building Block     GoogleNet (inception) Architecture   Refrences: https://www.coursera.org/learn/convolutional-neural-networks/home/week/2
https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/8281823/
https://papers.nips.cc/paper/4824-imagenet-classification-with-deep-convolutional-neural-networks.pdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My View on Quantum Computing</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/whatisquantumcomputing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 22:23:02 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/whatisquantumcomputing/</guid>
      <description>Invention is the necessity rather let it be defined as an incredibility. Quantum computing is an epitome justified to the sentence. Reviewing the civilization history, the hungers who made it happen are Isaac Chuang of the Los Alamos National Laboratory, Neil Gershenfeld of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), and Mark Kubinec of the University of California at Berkeley who first created the first quantum computer (2-qubit) that could be loaded with data and output a solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate Synthetic Images using DCGAN</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/dcgan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 21:10:35 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/dcgan/</guid>
      <description>GAN[1] is a method to teach deep learning model to capture training data so that we can generate duplicate (seems real) data. GAN consist of two models: Generator and Discriminator. Generator model tries to generate real like data and discriminator network tries to predict whether it is fake (generated data) or actually came from real data distribution. DCGAN[2] is the extened form (Image version) of original GAN idea. It mainly composes of convolution layers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My View On Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/myviewonai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 19:53:55 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gaudelbijay.github.io/blogs/myviewonai/</guid>
      <description>About a century ago an american computer scientist John McCarthy coined a term &amp;ldquo;Artificial Intilegence&amp;rdquo;. The science and engieneering develpoment of computer systems to perform tasks normally requiring human intillegence, such as visual perception, speech recognization, decision making and translation between languages. We can say we have achieved perfect artificial intillegence when all the applications of AI such as machine learning speech robotics natural language processing expert systems vision are achieved.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
